<DOC DOCNO="bn/cnn/01/cnn_0122@0122@cnn@bn@en@on">
<ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Israeli</ENAMEX> Prime Minister <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Ehud Barak</ENAMEX> is rejecting calls for a quick settlement with <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Palestinians</ENAMEX> to end the outbreak of violence in <ENAMEX TYPE="LOC">the Middle East</ENAMEX> .
During a meeting of his cabinet , <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Barak</ENAMEX> criticized members of his own political party who have urged him to finalize an agreement before President <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Clinton</ENAMEX> leaves office <ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">next month</ENAMEX> .
</DOC>
